da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
gulp!
Delicious!
Takutsuyan
Amazing!
Tatara!
Thank you for watching!
Hello everyone, I'm Nanami Konishi from Hyugaizaka 46.
It's windy.
Let me tell you where I am today.
Ja-jang, I'm near Sky Tree.
I love this street and I can see the river here.
I often go there in my private life.
Today I'd like to show you a little bit of my private life.
I'm going to climb Sky Tree.
For now, I'd like to head to Sky Tree on my walking road.
Usually, you can see the Skytree lit up.
But this time, they collaborated with Hinatazaka 46.
You can see the special lighting of the Hyugaizaka version.
It's supposed to light up in the color of the members' penlights!
I knew I had to see my own penlight.
That's what I got today.
That's what I'm looking forward to today.
I'm really looking forward to it!
I can't wait to see my own penlight color!
It's such a rare opportunity!
I'm really happy!
Thank you very much!
Tokyo Sky Tree
If I'm not careful like this, I can see the brightness of the sky!
Oh, by the way, I once took a picture
I took a picture of it in this park and posted it on my blog.
I took this picture with a ginkgo
It's a picture of him smiling.
I took it when I went with Haruharu
I posted it on my blog
It's a big place
The air is so green and beautiful
It's so beautiful
And there's a river next to it.
I can really feel the nature.
I like it.
It's my favorite place to walk.
Green and me.
I'm going to talk about something that's not important at all.
I'm going to tell you a story that's totally unimportant to me.
You know...
When I was asked to play the center of the song
the soundtrack was distributed ahead of time.
The soundtrack was distributed in advance.
It was raining that day.
And it was raining on the day it was released.
Isn't it amazing?
I'm not a rainy girl, but...
But it's so sunny today.
It's so beautiful.
Can you feel it?
Sunny skies!
Amazing!
Here we are!
Wow, we did it!
We're here!
I'm off to go shopping!
I'm off!
I'll go here.
Here...
This bakery.
At the bakery, with Rio.
Get some bread.
And we ate it together
I remember eating it together.
I have fond memories of that.
Wow.
I often buy clothes and birthday presents for people in Soramachi.
I've been there once, but I'd like to go again.
I want to go there and get something.
What is it?
Quick Konishi
What am I going to buy now?
Here we are. The correct answer is...
Ta-da!
Dried plums!
Look at this!
A lot of pickled plums!
What's more...
There is only one in the package.
This one
This one.
In the three places
Pick your favorite pickled plums
Pick three.
I only said three.
I'll buy them.
I can enjoy all kinds of pickled plums.
Kimchi plums! Wow!
What's a tangerine plum?
I like the honey and the mikan ume.
I'm a woman who doesn't worry.
I love karashimentaiko.
I wonder what kind of ume is used in karashimentaiko.
I'm so curious.
Rice piles?
Rice piled up
Inazumi Plum
I'll choose these three.
I'm not worried at all.
I'll definitely eat the pickled plums today.
Wait!
Wait, food samples I've loved since I was a child.
Aren't they great?
Look at this.
Amazing!
It's the Tokyo Sky Tree.
It's got
It's got a Tokyo Sky Tree pattern on it.
Oh, wait.
If it's this kind of chocolate, you can put it on your bag.
Look at this.
It's so small.
It's a tiny piece of chocolate.
Piece of chocolate.
I love it.
Look at this!
Wait a minute. There's too many cute ones.
I want to buy this for Micchan!
Dorayaki
Wow!
I bought it!
Yay, my chocolate!
I'll put it on my bag!
Before climbing the Sky Tree
There's an amazing festival going on.
What a surprise!
Let's get started!
Taiwan Festival
I love Taiwanese food.
I love Taiwanese food, especially fried food.
So I would like to get some of the famous fried food in Taiwan
I would like to get some and eat it!
Let's go!
Thank you very much!
Look at this!
It's huge!
What a face!
This is a half-sibling.
No way.
Does that mean it's another half of this?
Wow!
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
And at this size, it's boneless.
It's the best!
Delicious!
Windy
Windy.
But I'll keep eating it, it's delicious!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for the food
I finished it in an instant.
I can't eat one piece at all.
It's just a little bit windy.
I'm going to run away.
Oh, my God!
Look at this.
Each and every one of the members
Wall
There's Konishi.
What a time to have bangs!
How is it growing?
It's a miracle of stroking.
This is a photo of a miracle stroking.
We are collaborating on an event at the observation circuit and the observation deck.
I'm looking forward to seeing it!
It's nice to see!
Collaboration with Beyer
It's amazing!
I'm looking forward to
Look at that.
I'm going to go.
Amazing!
There are so many cherry blossoms!
What's more...
What's that music?
It's going up!
It's amazing!
Look at this!
Okay, I'll be careful.
It's bright, it's bright, it's bright.
Look!
Sasaka and Yoko are standing side by side.
Amazing!
Look at this!
It's really Hyuuga-zaka!
It's the elevator of Hyuhizaka!
I'm so moved.
I thought I was going to cry.
Watch out!
It's amazing.
Maybe it's too dark.
Shut up!
There's a live video of the Hinatazaka concert playing.
And it's on JYR.
It's the Hinata Travel Festival.
I'm so moved. I'm crying.
Thank you so much. This is amazing!
I've made an observation circuit.
Amazing!
I can already feel the waves.
Oh, my God, it's not going to change.
What do you think?
It's a sunny slope! I hear it!
Oh, there's Mr. Chiffo!
He's so cute! He's so cool!
Mr. Sifo!
Thank you for coming and signing our book.
Wow! Amazing!
Me too.
I want to sign it, too.
I wonder if I'm here.
That's nice.
I've never been to Sky Tree before, but it's the first time I've climbed it, and the first time I climbed it, my face is on it.
No, it's not.
I'm here.
I'll sign it.
I made it.
You should definitely go see it.
I'm here.
This is you, the newcomer.
I wonder...
Fox's probably sorry how old I am
A lot of Joyful Love music video costumes are on display
Hey everyone!
Picture books are also on display.
Amazing!
We went to the cafe!
So cute and colorful!
sodas and stuff!
So many colorful sodas!
Aren't they so cool? This one.
What? A collaboration menu?
Amazing!
Original poster for one item
One poster!
I'll have the double berry white milk.
I'll have this Double Berry White Milk!
The reason is
The
Blueberry & Raspberry
concept? I used it as a motif
with soda
of the 4th season's artwork
motif.
I thought it was the first time
I was so happy to see it.
I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
Blue Razz is one of my favorite songs.
It's great!
Yay!
I'm so excited!
Ta-da!
Oh! Dried fish!
Looks so good!
What's that on top?
Soft serve ice cream?
Ah!
Wait a minute. There's a random coaster in front of it.
Here we go. What is it? What do you think it is?
The correct answer is: Ta-da!
Konishi did it!
Yay! A landslide!
Bon appétit!
What's that? Maybe this is whipped cream!
It's whipped cream!
Smell it.
I thought it was cream.
I don't know what it smells like.
It's delicious.
It's milk.
It's milk, but...
But it's not sweet.
It's not just milk.
It's really delicious!
I finished it!
It was gone in an instant.
It was really delicious!
Thank you very much for the food.
After this, Tokyo Skytree
to do a special lighting for us.
I was looking forward to this the most today.
This is what I was looking forward to the most today!
I was so excited to see the Sky Tree in the color of my penlight.
I'm going to meet the Sky Tree in the color of my penlight!
I got out of the Sky Tree.
I'm on the ground.
It's so lonely
This is where I'm headed.
Oh, my God, you're Honeydew!
I took this picture of you.
This is the location of the jacket car
Haruyo and I
Haruyo and I took the photo
It's the place where
It's really in the center of the city.
Sky Tree can be seen
Sky Tree can be seen from the bridge.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
Juken Bridge
This step.
Haruyo-san climbs up to this guardrail.
I was at the bottom, and we talked about something like, "That's the Sky Tree, isn't it?
Yes, it was like a chapter.
I was able to take pictures while talking with Mr. Ariyoshi.
It's so beautiful!
This place is so romantic, isn't it?
I like it, it's so quiet.
I want to see the Sky Tree here alone in peace and quiet.
They say there are only 4 minutes left!
Four more minutes.
It's a very tense moment.
You can only see it for a moment. You can't miss it.
The colors are getting more and more like a rainbow!
Yo!
It's turning black.
Maybe it's starting.
Oh, oh, oh, here it comes, here it comes!
Blue.
That's the color of the day.
It's light blue.
Yay!
It's so beautiful!
I can't stop staring at it.
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Look at this.
Rainbow!
A rainbow!
It's so beautiful! Look at this! Isn't it amazing?
Rainbows are beautiful.
It changes like this?
It's changing like this.
After Joyful Love...
Here he comes!
Oh, blue, blue!
Blue!
What a special get!
He's got one thin leg!
This way.
Can you see the lighting?
Oh, my God! It's different, different, different...
Wait, there's one that keeps changing.
It's going to change pretty soon.
You'd better hurry.
Myself.
You better hurry up.
Oh!
Oh? Orange? Orange?
That's Mr. Nim, isn't it?
There's the orange one.
I've got an image.
Wait.
The fourth term will be here soon.
Yellow-green.
Oh, Haruyasu, doesn't that mean they're already here?
HaruYoru!
It's the 10th term Obashii!
Oh, here they come!
Tamagnum colors!
Tamagnum colors! Tamagnum colors!
Wait a minute, I'm coming, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Stone mound means...
That means the stone is coming today.
Boom, boom, boom!
Thump-thump-thump
Thump-thump-thump!
Oh, here it comes!
Wow! It's so beautiful! It's so beautiful!
Wow! Impressive! Oh, it's changed!
You could have shot my penlight-colored picture!
Three, two, one, drone!
Sand blast success! Yes!
I saw it for the first time!
It's the Sky Tree in my own penlight colors that I've longed for!
I took this picture by myself.
It's not a big picture. I took it just now.
So, please try to climb the Tokyo Sky Tree from the same walking road as me!
Yes, sir! Bye! Bye-bye! Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!